My sister was taken.
When's the last time you saw her?
When I was eight.
They believe her disappearance
is linked to sex trafficking.
You have a lead on your sister?
Man contacted the tip line. Marine.
Said she was working a corner.
Told him she thought her name was Shari.
Half the time. I think
if I turn around fast enough.
if the light's just right.
I'll see her there.
Always right there over my shoulder.
- And she still is.
- You want my help?
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
Hey.
Okay. Where are we headed today?
Got three new RedXpage ads
for potential working girls.
It's the same site where
that Marine said he met Shari.
They're all East Side.
None of them look too good
for her but could be a match.
All right. so East Side.
East Side.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
This is her at 6.
She'd be 28 now.
♪ ♪
I mean. it's been 22 years
since she was taken.
It's possible she's
still with her abductor.
Or she could have been sold.
Working for a new pimp.
Mm-hmm.
♪ ♪
Or she could have gotten
lost again. drugs. alcohol.
The likelihood that she was abused
further by someone else is high.
She could be anywhere. anything.
But I swear I'd know her if I saw her.
I'd still know her.
Are you sure this is it?
No. I'm just guessing.
She goes by Lila on the site.
can't really see her face clearly.
But it's the same RedXpage.
adds up with our timeline.
Police. anyone home?
Might be an old address.
Yeah.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
Voight.
What?
What is it?
Eva. listen.
I can...
♪ ♪
It's not Shari.
She looks like the girl
from the ad. though. Lila.
She's younger than I thought.
Not much bruising.
Yeah. stab wounds probably killed her.
There's no blood here. though.
It's a dump site.
Not recent.
Maybe 12 hours.
This is only a 1/2 inch.
- Yeah. but it's deep.
- See the sides?
Yeah. the knife had a blade guard.
All right. I'm gonna call the crime lab.
I'll get the team down here.
♪ ♪
[SIGHS]
Imani?
Sir. this is Shari.
The girl on the left. that's my sister.
♪ ♪
Synced & corrected by -robtor-
www.addic7ed.com
All right. prints popped in the system.
Her real name is Laura Kerr.
multiple priors
for solicitation and possession.
No family.
Sorry. I don't understand.
You were here running her?
Why?
We're eliminating her as a possible
in a missing persons case.
It's Imani's sister. Her name is Shari.
She went missing at six years old
from Imani's family home.
Recent tips suggested
she was in Chicago.
had been sex trafficked.
Imani and I have been
working on the side.
It's not a match. obviously.
But there may still
be a connection. okay?
We're taking the homicide.
There is a connection.
That was Shari on her phone.
All right. so run
Laura's phone contacts.
all her movements last night.
And start building a timeline.
And run all the DNA inside that trailer.
Shari's will pop.
They were definitely friends.
They might even have the same pimp.
All right. that's her
trailer right there.
No one's set foot inside except us.
Let's do a full sweep.
Witnesses?
Well. patrol's already
started knock-and-talks.
But I want us to take over.
We run this ourselves.
I wanna know everyone who visited Laura.
if she worked tricks at home.
Dante.
Just find out who she
was with last night.
Come on.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Police. I need your camera footage.
The hell are you doing?
What do you mean. what footage?
- What are you talking about?
- Ma'am...
You've been loud all morning long.
I already told the man...
Ma'am. there's a camera in your window.
Where does the footage go?
- What?
- Where does the footage go?
Is it a link to an app on your phone?
What is it?
I don't think you're
supposed to be in my house.
Ma'am. ma'am. we just...
we just need the footage.
Please.
♪ ♪
Come on.
Wait a minute.
I'm still running
the rest of the footage.
but this is the cleanest image.
You can't see the vehicle clearly.
but there's no vehicle
registered to Laura's name.
So my best guess is it belongs
to a john or our pimp.
All right. anything on
Laura's last movements?
No.
We could rerun these images
by the residents.
do a second knock-and-talk
to see if anyone
remembers the vehicle.
All right. We got her phone records?
We should have those soon.
Ruzek's on it.
- ME?
- Still working.
The autopsy preliminary suggests that
the cause of death was
due to sharp force injury.
We're gonna learn more from the ME soon.
But they think the knife was either
a stiletto or a switchblade
based on the shape and size
of the flat guard indentations.
All right. shout at me when
you get those phone records.
Imani.
- Imani.
- Yeah?
Give me a minute.
I also ran the address
for all in-service calls.
No pops for solicitation.
which doesn't mean much
because police doesn't frequent
that park often. so...
- We're gonna work everything.
- I know.
Every lead on your sister.
I know.
Look. I need you to tell me
that you also know
we're working a young woman's homicide.
I know.
I need you to tell me...
I know what you're asking me. okay?
I can work it.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Saliva sample from a beer
bottle in Laura's trailer
matched Shari's DNA.
You were right. She was there.
♪ ♪
Hey. I got the GPS data
from Laura's phone.
It's good.
So there's not much in contacts.
No Shari listed.
But Laura's last tower ping came back
to a complex on West 109th.
Place has multiple vice complaints.
priors for solicitation.
And it was the site of Operation Angel.
which unfortunately went nowhere.
Habitual prostitution site.
It's the last place Laura's phone pinged
before her trailer last night.
Let's hit it.
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Move.
Blood.
Chicago PD!
Clear!
Clear.
Laura was attacked here. bled out.
All right. we found
the kill site. unit 2D.
Roll the crime lab.
- Take in anyone you see.
- Copy. 5021.
Crime lab's en route.
♪ ♪
[GROANS]
[GULPS]
Excuse me. sir.
Can I talk to you for a second?
[FOREBODING MUSIC]
Hey. hey!
Police! Stop!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[GRUNTING]
- Stop the car!
- No!
[GRUNTS]
[BRAKES SCREECH]
[CAR HORN HONKS] [GRUNTS]
Are you kidding me?
[GRUNTING]
Stay down!
Do not resist!
Do not!
Stop!
[GROANS]
I'm not gonna keep
asking you. all right?
It is a simple question.
Give me a simple answer.
- Why did you run?
- I panicked.
Because of how you got
those injuries on your face?
How did you get them?
We're gonna find out one way or another.
Imani. the ambo's here.
You should get your legs checked.
You were here last night.
You saw a girl. It went wrong.
So what. you hurt 'em? You killed 'em?
- What? No. no!
- You killed her. didn't you?
No. of course I didn't kill anyone!
Then why does your face look like that?
- Why did you run?
- I didn't hurt them.
- They attacked me.
- Okay.
I didn't touch them!
- They did this.
- Okay. How is that?
I... I met them here. Yes.
Working girls.
Yes. okay. fine. Yes.
But once I got here. they jumped me.
They attacked me. They took my wallet.
I couldn't report it.
Of course not.
Good. So why'd you come back?
I... I thought my phone was here.
But I didn't touch either of them.
I ran from them. I left.
- And then they were fine...
- Was this them?
Yes. yes.
- Yes?
- Yes. Yes.
Lila and Sable.
He's lying.
He's lying. He knows more.
He's probably good for it.
You get anything else?
Fowler's in with Atwater now.
He gave us a timeline.
Said he left the unit at 1:30 a.m.
His GPS says the same.
So does his wife.
He also claims that
he saw them get dropped off
by a black BMW. male driver. white.
40s. 50s. tough looking.
Could be their pimp.
We're processing the vehicle right now.
We're running it.
He didn't get the girls off of RedX.
He got them off a different site.
Embrazia.
- He said her name was Sable.
- Shari.
He could still be lying.
He could have killed Laura
and had their pimp
dispose of her body.
Well. either way. we need more.
Let's dig into Embrazia.
All right. there's no page
for Shari. Sable either.
Ran her picture. It's not there.
All right. Laura is.
This might be something.
This girl. Kat. she's got
the same profile as Laura.
same language. same codes.
Doesn't pop in any other pages.
Okay. so it probably means
she got the same guy
- running her. same pimp.
- Mm-hmm.
This could be our man.
What... uh. what's that number?
She's got an SMS number used to book.
Does Laura?
- No.
- Where does the SMS go?
If there's a phone. we got a location.
So what am I looking at?
We tracked the SMS to a burner.
The burner is still on.
It's pinging inside that house.
The place is abandoned.
but it's been indexed to hell
by Narcotics.
Vice. Area Central.
It is a known trap house.
Yeah. it sounds like
it's just a junky crash pad
known for deals
and small-time trafficking.
It's owned by nobody in particular.
So could just walk
right through the front door.
And burn it as a lead.
If the phone is pinging inside.
then our pimp could be there now.
Shari could be there.
And if we move and she's not there.
there's zero chance she'll ever come.
We can sit on it.
Yeah. let's... let's
set up surveillance.
We'll see who's there.
[CRICKETS CHIRPING]
Two hours. No one in. no one out.
Whoever's there is there for the night.
We don't know that.
What. 'cause junkies got
late night errands to run?
- We're not burning it.
- If the phone is in there...
If. if. you know why you keep saying if?
Because there's a margin for error.
Well. then let me go UC.
Look. I'll go in there.
I'll search for the targets.
If they're not in there.
I slip right back out here.
and we sit here again.
I'm not gonna burn anything.
Torres. you good to go UC?
10-4.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
Yo.
What up?
Hey. who the hell are you?
I'm just here to pick up. man.
Hey. that ain't no answer.
That's the best you're getting.
I don't know you.
Were we supposed to know you?
[LAUGHTER]
What you picking up?
That is none of your business.
[LAUGHTER]
Bro. I'm messing.
- [LAUGHS]
- I don't care what you pick up.
Just don't fool with nobody except
who you picking up from.
Ain't none of the drinks here are free.
- Go on up.
- All right.
- Hey.
- What?
Go on up that way.
Ah.
[LAUGHTER]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
What?
- Occupied.
- Oh. my bad.
- Can I help you?
- Shut the door.
- Yo. Do you go by Kat?
- Whoa. whoa.
Hey. drop it.
What the hell do you think
you're doing? Ow.
Is your name... yeah. you're Kat.
- What are you doing?
- Do you know these women?
Do you know... yes or no. do you...
- Get out of my room.
- Do you know these women?
No. I don't know them
and I don't know who the hell you are
and I don't know what you're doing.
- Yo! Kat. you in there?
- Hey.
I'm police. all right?
Do you want them to know
you're in here with police?
I'm not trying to put you in danger.
Relax.
Yo. yo. yo. baby girl. You deaf?
[KNOCK AT DOOR]
- Giggi said you was in here.
- Do you know these women?
Hmm?
Are you out?
One of them is my sister. all right?
I'm just looking for my sister.
Just tell me the truth. please.
Hey. if you shot all that.
bro. I swear to God. Kat.
All right. Do you know them?
Okay.
Is the man who's running them here?
[BANGING ON DOOR]
All right. I'm gonna let you go.
You're gonna tell him you're fine.
and he'll never know
you came with us. okay?
Nod if you understand.
Yo. is someone else
in there with my girl?
Don't.
Screw off. Broaca!
Is someone else in there?
Give me a minute!
I got my goddamn period. you fool!
I was in the bathroom!
Stop slamming the house in!
♪ ♪
- If Laura was murdered...
- [STAMMERS] She was.
And I don't know you from George.
- What?
- That's the expression.
Hey. Kat. look.
The photos are real.
No one's lying to you.
Now. you knew Laura. right?
Yeah. once.
But I don't trick no more.
I haven't seen them in months.
Like I said. I don't have
numbers or addresses for them.
- I got Broaca now.
- Okay.
I'm with him. so I don't run
with those girls no more.
Your picture was still on the site.
Yo. there's girls from
ten years ago on that site.
- All right.
- I forgot to take it down.
But you knew Laura. right?
You said you knew Laura.
So do you know Shari?
Do you know anything?
I don't know... Jesus! How many times...
Okay. hey. hey. hey.
Let's just take it back.
You said you ran with them.
What did you mean by that?
Hmm?
Hey. Kat. look at me.
We are working a murder. Okay?
A couple of tricks.
that means nothing to us.
Believe me.
Come on.
All right.
I liked them. Laura and Shari.
They were cool.
And I needed some cash.
So I... I let Shari's man
run me for a bit.
And then. you know.
when the girls wanted
to take things into
their own hands. I thought...
[SCOFFS] Okay. why the hell not?
And then I met Broaca.
so I don't do that no more.
You honey-trapped your johns.
Yeah. it was easier than...
- Hey.
- Yeah.
Kat. who is running them?
Who is Shari's man?
Girl. your sister's married.
Okay?
Her husband runs her.
And he...
it's bad.
[APPREHENSIVE MUSIC]
He roughs her up.
She always got marks around her neck.
Okay. okay.
I need a name. give me a name.
Kirby. Russ.
- Address.
- I... I don't know.
I legit don't. okay?
I always met them out...
at Lucky's mostly.
Description. Give me something.
White. 50s.
Big. but. like. small-john
muscle if you know what I mean.
♪ ♪
Did Kirby know you were robbing johns?
Hell no. If he knew. he'd kill us.
Kat's description of Kirby
matches Fowley's description
of the man at the scene to a T.
Hands around the neck.
same injuries as Laura.
So Kirby pulled up early the night of.
discovered the girls
were beating their johns.
He got pissed and he killed Laura.
And he doesn't want it
connected to that building.
so he dumps the body near the trailer.
All right. I got him.
He's got a license.
but not much of a footprint.
No car. no mortgage.
And Social Security number
comes back to a boy
who died in 2007
in Jackson. Mississippi.
Okay. stolen identity.
- Anything on the wife?
- No.
There's gotta be something else.
No. he just... he doesn't
have that much of a record.
- Okay. keep running that ID.
- All right.
If Kirby killed Laura. then that means
that we don't know
that Shari's safe with him.
- Hey. come on.
- He could be... you know...
Hey. let's go to Lucky's.
[HIP-HOP MUSIC PLAYING]
Take it off. baby.
♪ Making money
every time you dance. girl ♪
Yeah.
♪ Making money
every time you dance. girl ♪
♪ I don't want nobody else ♪
♪ I want you all to myself ♪
♪ I don't want no... ♪
Excuse me.
Sergeant Voight with
Chicago Police Department.
Wondering if you remember
a girl who might have
worked here by the name of Sable?
Mm-hmm. I knew Sable.
Sweet. sweet girl.
Always had her nose in a book.
Why?
Is she in trouble. officer?
No. not at all.
We're just trying to find her.
When did you speak to her last?
I don't know. A couple months.
Things get blurry around here.
You want a dance?
Oh. no. thank you.
I'll give you the CPD discount.
I appreciate it. Thank you very much.
You police?
You gonna make my day
and shut this place down?
I'm looking for Sable.
She bounced months ago.
I don't know where she went.
left with her husband.
- Kirby?
- Yeah.
Was hoping she'd leave
without him. but. uh. no luck.
Well. why's that?
♪ I want you all to myself ♪
I'm... I'm her sister.
♪ ♪
♪ Body bang like chains on my neck ♪
Look. Kirby used to pimp her
out in the parking lot.
All right?
I know I should have tried
to shut it down. and...
I just didn't know what I was
supposed to do. okay?
♪ ♪
And you haven't heard from her?
No. no.
She just didn't clock in one day.
And then it was radio silence.
♪ Making money
every time you dance. girl ♪
I'm sorry.
Did she clean out her locker?
[MUFFLED MUSIC PLAYING]
♪ ♪
[TENSE MUSIC]
- Anything?
- Venture card's good.
CTA hit us back with
a credit card attached to a car.
belongs to Sara Jane Kirby.
That's her.
And there's an LKA.
a house in Bridgeport.
- All right. she have a sheet?
- Can't find a damn thing.
Far as I could tell.
she didn't exist before 2023.
Start typing up a warrant.
Request a no-knock.
We move as quiet as possible.
♪ ♪
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC]
- Clear.
Clear.
It's clear. No one's here.
Switch to inventory search.
Keep your lights low.
We'll give it three minutes.
Then go outside and hold anchor.
♪ ♪
We got a car rolling up in the front.
Unrelated. disregard.
[SOFT LAUGH]
Is that Farsi?
It's a quote from a book.
"Saying goodbye is a little like dying."
[SOFT MUSIC]
♪ ♪
There's years of stuff in here.
Take pictures.
♪ ♪
Imani.
[CAMERA SHUTTER CLICKING]
They had the same last name
since she was a kid.
He was pretending
to be her father. and...
then he went from father to husband.
This is... it's him.
He's... he's the one that...
he took her at six.
- Time's up.
- All right. we gotta go.
Imani.
Come on. let's go.
♪ ♪
All right. Atwater's
holding anchor with Tact.
Hopefully they come back.
Kev will move on 'em.
Rest of us. we dig in to Kirby.
Look. he would've needed help getting
all those fake IDs and passports.
There's gonna be a trail.
He could be running.
Or getting a new identity.
So let's dig fast.
Come on. let's go. Come on.
Seven identities over 20 years.
it's a lot to sift through.
All right. one of these aliases
does have a car registered to him.
It's outdated. but it's worth a BOLO.
I've seen this hologram before.
Where?
Southside Hustlers.
Do you remember that credit card scheme.
the raid I joined up in OT?
They made fakes.
Detective Albini?
This is Torres. Intelligence.
[VOICES FADING]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
[DISTANT] Imani?
Imani?
Imani.
What? What you got?
Air.
No. I'm... I'm good.
Yeah. so... so get some air.
Nothing is gonna happen without you.
[EXHALES]
[DISTANT SIREN WAILING]
You know. we used to buy these together.
We'd save up our allowance and
we'd go to the corner store.
We liked to hold them in our cheeks
to see how long
the sweetness would last.
She had a pack of these in that house.
She was in that house.
She was.
She's been with that man all her life.
I gotta find her.
[PHONE BUZZING]
Hey. Mark.
Hey. thanks.
Yeah. thanks for the call. man.
Oh. yeah. Okay.
So... so he was picked up before. yeah?
All right. Yeah. no.
That's helpful. That's helpful.
Hey. next round's on me. all right?
All right.
I got a name. Marius Palmer.
Hustler who used to steal the bank
plastic to make fake credit cards.
Marius Palmer. M-A-R-I-U-S?
Yeah. served two years
in Stateville for felony fraud.
got out on bail six months ago.
He's still got a place that's
not far from Kirby's house
down on the South Side.
What if they're still in touch?
What if he knows where Kirby is
and how we can reach him?
- It's a long shot.
- Well. it's what we got.
Yeah. I'll loop in Voight.
[KNOCKING]
What's up. man?
What's going on? Who are you?
I'm just a guy who wants to
put some cash in your pocket.
Yeah. we heard you got
some digits for sale.
Yeah? Where you hear that from?
Your boy. TW.
He's in with my cousin at Stateville.
Mm-hmm. Yeah. you've been misinformed.
And as much as I would like to help you.
little sweetheart. yeah. I'm retired.
Come on. man.
Come on. man. Look. we're in a jam.
Well. go fix your jam somewhere else.
Move along.
[MUFFLED SPEECH]
Who you got in there?
- None of your business.
- Why not?
Back up. Chicago PD.
- Back up.
- Man. you can't do this.
Don't move. I got him. Don't move.
The hell is y'all doing. man?
Y'all can't come in my house like this.
Hey. Get down on the ground!
Police! Hands!
Torres!
It's him! It's Kirby!
[DRAMATIC MUSIC]
Stop!
I said stop!
♪ ♪
[TIRES SCREECH] Damn it.
5021 Union. I got
a homicide suspect. Russ Kirby.
driving a black BMW southbound
in an alley on Adams and 33rd Street.
I just lost eyes. I need a perimeter.
I need cars. Get me cars now!
Copy. 5021 Union. Backup en route.
♪ ♪
[TIRES SCREECH]
I see him. I got eyes on Kirby.
Illinois tags.
John. 5. 7. King. Sam. 1. 8.
Voight. I need everyone here now.
Kirby was at that house.
Shari's gotta be close.
She's gotta be here somewhere.
She could even be at that house...
I hear you. I'm coming your way.
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [CAR HORN HONKING]
- Come on! Move!
♪ ♪
I lost him.
I lost eyes on the black BMW.
Does anyone see him?
He was last seen
on Adams and 28th Street.
Union. we have no eyes.
Well. then keep looking.
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
- Copy.
- Excuse me. sir. Sir.
Did you see a black BMW... a black...
♪ ♪
Police.
[SIREN WAILING]
Squad 1229. do you see him?
Negative. we don't have eyes.
Well. keep searching.
He's gotta be around here somewhere.
- Imani. do you copy?
- Try South Green.
Copy you.
Imani. you there?
Yeah. go for Imani.
I got her.
- What?
- I've got Shari.
It's her.
- You...
- She was at the house.
I've got her.
She's secure.
[PANTING]
We got her. Imani.
We got her.
[SOFT DRAMATIC MUSIC]
♪ ♪
- She's upstairs.
- Is she okay?
Yeah. she's safe.
We waited for you to begin.
♪ ♪
Interrogation.
Here. give me your gun.
♪ ♪
Who the hell are you?
[WOLF HOWLS]
[TENSE MUSIC]
♪ ♪
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm